<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Do not go gentle into this good night. Rage.</title>
    <link>https://embano1.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Do not go gentle into this good night. Rage.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 22:17:38 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://embano1.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes and the fine art of scaling - UP!</title>
      <link>https://embano1.github.io/post/vpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 22:17:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://embano1.github.io/post/vpa/</guid>
      <description>Do you know these days, when a certain topic you have thought about a while hits you again and again?
It so happened to me last week, when I first discussed the topic of distributed runtime (read Kubernetes) optimization with Emad Benjamin, Chief Technologist/ Application Platforms at VMware (make sure to follow him on Twitter). The idea was mainly about day two operations for distributed systems written for and running on Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Informers - What´s the difference?</title>
      <link>https://embano1.github.io/post/k8s_informers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 20:11:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://embano1.github.io/post/k8s_informers/</guid>
      <description>This post not only is about Kubernetes´ Client-Go SDK Informers, but also marks my first blog post ever. Celebration! Feel free to skip over my sentimental way of saying &amp;ldquo;Thank you&amp;rdquo; in the next paragraph and directly jump into a little bit of research on Client-Go Informers ;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why would I want to blog?</title>
      <link>https://embano1.github.io/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 19:17:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://embano1.github.io/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;@bbrundert is the answer (to almost everything btw).
Well, if it wasn´t Björn who finally kicked my &amp;lt;redacted&amp;gt;, I think I´d never started my own blog. I´m pretty active on Twitter (@embano1), and never felt the need to share more than 140 characters with the world. But I changed my view last week, after some glass of wine at Björn´s &amp;ldquo;Home Sweet Home&amp;rdquo;. Our discussion went like this:
 &amp;lt;Bla bla Kubernetes bla bla&amp;hellip;&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>