<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Do not go gentle into this good night. Rage.</title>
    <link>https://embano1.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Do not go gentle into this good night. Rage.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 22:04:27 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://embano1.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>QoS, &#34;Node allocatable&#34; and the Kubernetes Scheduler</title>
      <link>https://embano1.github.io/post/sched-reconcile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 22:04:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://embano1.github.io/post/sched-reconcile/</guid>
      <description>What a title, sorry for that&amp;hellip;Weeks ago, I started a post about a customer question which came up during a workshop. I just didn´t find the time to finish it, because of &amp;hellip; other stuff. Also a BIG thanks to my Twitter fellows @bbrundert, @mhausenblas and @timoreimann for their review and feedback to improve this post. Make sure to follow them!
Some useful background reading:  Managing Compute Resources for Containers How does the Kubernetes scheduler work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes and the fine art of scaling - UP!</title>
      <link>https://embano1.github.io/post/vpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 22:17:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://embano1.github.io/post/vpa/</guid>
      <description>Do you know these days, when a certain topic you have thought about a while hits you again and again?
It so happened to me last week, when I first discussed the topic of distributed runtime (read Kubernetes) optimization with Emad Benjamin, Chief Technologist/ Application Platforms at VMware (make sure to follow him on Twitter). The idea was mainly about day two operations for distributed systems written for and running on Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why would I want to blog?</title>
      <link>https://embano1.github.io/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 19:17:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://embano1.github.io/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;@bbrundert is the answer (to almost everything btw).
Well, if it wasn´t Björn who finally kicked my &amp;lt;redacted&amp;gt;, I think I´d never started my own blog. I´m pretty active on Twitter (@embano1), and never felt the need to share more than 140 characters with the world. But I changed my view last week, after some glass of wine at Björn´s &amp;ldquo;Home Sweet Home&amp;rdquo;. Our discussion went like this:
 &amp;lt;Bla bla Kubernetes bla bla&amp;hellip;&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>